let questions = [
  {
    "numb": 1,
    "question": "I observe a bird take a tick out of another bird's head and eat it. In the social context, this behavior is known as",
    "answer": "allo grooming",
    "options": [
      "tick hunting",
      "auto grooming",
      "allo grooming",
      "foraging"
    ]
},

{
    "numb": 2,
    "question": "The scientific study of animal behavior is known as",
    "answer": "ethology",
    "options": [
      "behaviorism",
      "ecology",
      "ethology",
      "prey-predator dynamics"
    ]
},

{
    "numb": 3,
    "question": "Trampling of grass due to the movement of animals is an example of",
    "answer": "amensalism",
    "options": [
      "mutualism",
      "amensalism",
      "commensalism",
      "protocooperation"
    ]
},

{
    "numb": 4,
    "question": "Birds on a giraffe are an example of",
    "answer": "protocooperation",
    "options": [
      "colony",
      "commensalism",
      "protocooperation",
      "allelopathy"
    ]
},

{
    "numb": 5,
    "question": "I observe a monkey take a tick out of another monkey's head and eat it. In the social context, this behavior would be called",
    "answer": "allo grooming",
    "options": [
      "tick hunting",
      "auto grooming",
      "allo grooming",
      "foraging"
    ]
},

{
    "numb": 6,
    "question": "Hamilton's rule can be stated as",
    "answer": "rB > C",
    "options": [
      "rB < C",
      "rB > C",
      "rB = C",
      "rB + C = 0"
    ]
},

{
    "numb": 7,
    "question": "Egrets with buffaloes are an example of",
    "answer": "commensalism",
    "options": [
      "colony",
      "commensalism",
      "protocooperation",
      "allelopathy"
    ]
},

{
    "numb": 8,
    "question": "The interaction between exotic shrubs and trees through the action of seed predators is an example of",
    "answer": "apparent competition",
    "options": [
      "intraspecific competition",
      "apparent competition",
      "disguised competition",
      "harmonious competition"
    ]
},

{
    "numb": 9,
    "question": "Harmonious interaction occurs where",
    "answer": "both participants are unharmed",
    "options": [
      "at least one participant is benefited",
      "at least one participant is unharmed",
      "both participants are benefited",
      "both participants are unharmed"
    ]
},

{
    "numb": 10,
    "question": "An inventory of behaviors exhibited by an animal during a behavior exercise is called",
    "answer": "ethogram",
    "options": [
      "ecogram",
      "ethogram",
      "behaviourogram",
      "animalogram"
    ]
}
]